{ "data" : 
[
 {
   "Round":1,
   "TeamName": 1,
   "Question": "Which network topology requires Terminator?",
   "Option1": "Bus",
   "Option2": "Star",
   "Option3": "Ring",
   "Option4": "Mesh",
   "Option5": "All the Above",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Bus",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":1,
   "TeamName": 2,
   "Question": "Which protocol is used to automatically provide IP addresses to network computers?",
   "Option1": "IGMP",
   "Option2": "DNS",
   "Option3": "ARP",
   "Option4": "DHCP",
   "Option5": "All the Above",
   "CorrectAnswer": "DHCP",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":1,
   "TeamName": 3,
   "Question": "Which protocol is used to resolve IP to MAC addresses?",
   "Option1": "DNS",
   "Option2": "ARP",
   "Option3": "WEP",
   "Option4": "DHCP",
   "Option5": "None of the Above",
   "CorrectAnswer": "ARP",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":2,
   "TeamName": 1,
   "Question": "Which one was the initial name of Java?",
   "Option1": "Oak",
   "Option2": "CDL",
   "Option3": "CS-4",
   "Option4": "Usenet",
   "Option5": "None of the Above",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Oak",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":2,
   "TeamName": 2,
   "Question": "Which one was the first browser to support Java applets?",
   "Option1": "Internet Explorer",
   "Option2": "Safari",
   "Option3": "HotJava",
   "Option4": "NetJava",
   "Option5": "Firefox",
   "CorrectAnswer": "HotJava",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":2,
   "TeamName": 3,
   "Question": "Which two are valid constructors for thread?\n 1)Thread(Runnable r, string Name)\n 2)Thread()\n 3)Thread(int priority)\n 4)Thread(Runnable r,ThreadGroup g)\n 5)Thread(Runnable r,int priority)",
   "Option1": "1,3",
   "Option2": "2,4",
   "Option3": "1,2",
   "Option4": "2,5",
   "Option5": "3,5",
   "CorrectAnswer": "1,2",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":3,
   "TeamName": 1,
   "Question": "Which of the following is a server side JavaScript object?",
   "Option1": "Date",
   "Option2": "File",
   "Option3": "Function",
   "Option4": "File Upload",
   "Option5": "Both 2 and 4",
   "CorrectAnswer": "File",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":3,
   "TeamName": 2,
   "Question": "How does java script store dates in object of datatype?",
   "Option1": "The number of days since January 1st, 1900",
   "Option2": "The number of seconds since January 1st, 1970",
   "Option3": "The number of milliseconds since January 1st, 1970",
   "Option4": "The number of picoseconds since January 1st, 1970",
   "Option5": "The number of nanoseconds since January 1st, 1970",
   "CorrectAnswer": "The number of milliseconds since January 1st, 1970",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":3,
   "TeamName": 3,
   "Question": "What java wrapper type is created when a JavaScript object is sent to Java? ",
   "Option1": "ScriptObject",
   "Option2": "JavaObject",
   "Option3": "Jobject",
   "Option4": "JSObject",
   "Option5": "None of the Above",
   "CorrectAnswer": "JSObject",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":4,
   "TeamName": 1,
   "Question": "What is the data structure that a Set uses to store its elements?",
   "Option1": "Array",
   "Option2": "Object",
   "Option3": "Map",
   "Option4": "ArrayList",
   "Option5": "All the Above",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Map",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":4,
   "TeamName": 2,
   "Question": "Which collection class allows you to grow or shrink its size and provides indexed access to its elements, but whose methods are not synchronized?",
   "Option1": "Java.util.List",
   "Option2": "java.until.ArrayList",
   "Option3": "java.until.HashSet",
   "Option4": "java.until.Map",
   "Option5": "java.until.LinkedHashSet",
   "CorrectAnswer": "java.until.ArrayList",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":4,
   "TeamName": 3,
   "Question": "If you were to store objects into an implementation of List which happens only once in the entire lifecycle of the product, but reading these objects inside the List implementation is quite high, then which one would you use?",
   "Option1": "Vector",
   "Option2": "LinkedList",
   "Option3": "ArrayList",
   "Option4": "All the Above",
   "Option5": "None of the Above",
   "CorrectAnswer": "ArrayList",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":5,
   "TeamName": 1,
   "Question": "Following code will result in: float num=5/0",
   "Option1": "Compilation error: Divisions must be in try block",
   "Option2": "Complication error: DividebyZeroexception",
   "Option3": "Runtime Exception",
   "Option4": "No error: num is NaN",
   "Option5": "Compilation error: Number format exception occurred",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Runtime Exception",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":5,
   "TeamName": 2,
   "Question": "What happens during execution if a negative value is used for an array index?",
   "Option1": "An IndexOutOfBoundsException is thrown",
   "Option2": "A numberFormatException is thrown",
   "Option3": "The first slot of the array is used.",
   "Option4": "This is an error so the program immediately terminates no matter what",
   "Option5": "RunTime Exception",
   "CorrectAnswer": "An IndexOutOfBoundsException is thrown",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
   "Round":5,
   "TeamName": 3,
   "Question": "Waht is the only type of the exception that is NOT checked",
   "Option1": "Class Exception",
   "Option2": "Class RunTimeException and its subclasses",
   "Option3": "Class IOException and its subclasses",
   "Option4": "Class ArithmeticException only",
   "Option5": "FileNotFoundException",
   "CorrectAnswer": "Class IOException and its subclasses",
   "SelectedAnswer": ""
 }
]
}